Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Billington, Sandra (Box 770)
- Bin Faraj, Shuwaykh, 1922- (Box 771)
- Bing (Box 772)
- Bini, Maria Pia (Box 773)
- Binz (Box 774)
- Biografia (Box 775)
- Biographies of Celebrated Scholars in the World (Box 776)
- Biological Techniques (Box 777)
- Biomedical Telemetry (Box 778)
- Bipartisan Foreign Policy (Box 779)
- Bird, J.C. (John Clement), 1933- (Box 780)
- Birge, Edward A. (Box 781)
- Birkhimer (Box 782)
- Birnbacher (Box 783)
- Birth and Fortune (Box 784)
- Bischoff, Karl, 1905- (Box 785)
- Bishop, L. (Box 786)
- Bismarck, Otto (subject) (Box 787)
- Bissey, Luther Trauger (Box 788)
- Bitter (Box 789)
- Bizard, Francois (Box 790)
- Bjoernson, Bjoernstjerne (subject) (Box 791)
- Black, F. (Box 792)
- Black, William Galt (Box 793)
- Black Hawk (Box 794)
- Black Queen Stories (Box 795)
- Blackburne (Box 796)
- Blacks in Alabama, 1528-1865 (Box 797)
- Blackthunder, Elijah (Box 798)
- Blaga, Corneliu S. (Box 799)
- Blair, Hugh (Box 800)
- Blake, F. (Box 801)
- Blake, William (Poems) (Box 802)
- Blakeney, Edward Henry, 1869- (Box 803)
- Blanchard, D. (Box 804)
- Blanco (Box 805)
- Blane (Box 806)
- Blaschke, W. (Box 807)
- Blatt (Box 808)
- Blazejak, M. (Box 809)
- Bleibtreu (Box 810)
- Bley (Box 811)
- Bliss (Box 812)
- Bloch, E. (Box 813)
- Block, H. (Box 814)
- Blok, A. (subject) (Box 815)
- Blondel, G. (Box 816)
- Bloom, C. (Box 817)
- Bloomfield, R. (Box 818)
- Bloy (Box 819)
- Blucher, W. (Box 820)
- Blum, O. (Box 821)
- Blumenthal, K. (Box 822)
- Blunt, J. (Box 823)
- Boada, E. (Box 824)
- Boardman family (Box 825)
- Bobb, B. (Box 826)
- Boccaccio, G. (Box 827)
- Boccard (Box 828)
- Bock, I. (Box 829)
- Bode, W. (Box 830)
- Bodkin (Box 831)
- Bodmer, K. (Box 832)
- Boeckler, C. (Box 833)
- Boehm (Box 834)
- Boehringer (Box 835)
- Boening (Box 836)
- Boers (Box 837)
- Boettcher (Box 838)
- Bogart (Box 839)
- Boggs (Box 840)
- Bogota. Instituto Colombiano de Especializacion (Box 841)
- Bohemian San Francisco (Box 842)
- Bohun (Box 843)
- Bois (Box 844)
- Boisvert, J. (Box 845)
- Bokor, A. (Box 846)
- Bolen, C. (Box 847)
- Boletin La escoba (Box 848)
- Bolivar, S. (continued) (Box 849)
- Bolivia (Laws, statutes, etc.) (Box 850)
- Bolle (Box 851)
- Bollman (Box 852)
- Bolshevists (Box 853)
- Bolton, S. (Box 854)
- Bombay (State) (Box 855)
- Bonaccioli, A. (Box 856)
- Bonaventure, St. (Box 857)
- Bond, J. (Box 858)
- Bone, M. (Box 859)
- Bonham (Box 860)
- Bonin (Box 861)
- Bonne (Box 862)
- Bonner kunstverein (Box 863)
- Bonnycastle (Box 864)
- Bonville family (Box 865)
- Book of C. (Box 866)
- Book of short stories (Box 867)
- Bookman (Box 868)
- Boone (Box 869)
- Booth, J. (Box 870)
- Borah, W. (Box 871)
- Borchert, H. (Box 872)
- Borden, R. (Box 873)
- Borel, Eugene (Box 874)
- Borges, Jorge L. (Box 875)
- Boring (surname) (Box 876)
- Bormann, F. (Box 877)
- Bornkessel, W. (Box 878)
- Borredon (Box 879)
- Borsos (Box 880)
- Bosanquet, Bernard (author) (Box 881)
- Bosco, M. (Box 882)
- Bosley (Box 883)
- Bossert (Box 884)
- Boston (Place) (Author) R (Box 885)
- Boston. National (Box 886)
- Boston Colloquium (Box 887)
- Boston. Public Library (continued) (Box 888)
- Bostwick family (Box 889)
- Bosworth, N. (Box 890)
- Botev, Hristo (Box 891)
- Botswana. Ministry of F. (Box 892)
- Bottom High to the Crowd (Box 893)
- Boucher, Anthony, 1911-1968 (Box 894)
- Boudin (Box 895)
- Bouilly (Box 896)
- Bouligny (Box 897)
- Bouquet, Christian (Box 898)
- Bourdon (Box 899)
- Bourgogne (Box 900)
- Bourne, Michael O. (Box 901)
- Boussinot, Roger, 1921- (Box 902)
- Bouvier (Box 903)
- Bovista (Box 904)
- Bowen, Eliza (Box 905)
- Bower family (Box 906)
- Bowler (Box 907)
- Bowman, John C. (Box 908)
- Boxhorn (Box 909)
- Boyd, G. (Box 910)
- Boyer, Adolphe (Box 911)
- Boyle, L. (Box 912)
- Boys' h. (Box 913)
- Brabant (Box 914)
- Brack (Box 915)
- Braddell, D. (Box 916)
- Bradford (West Yorkshire) (Box 917)
- Bradley, O. (Box 918)
- Brady, D. (Box 919)
- Bragagnolo, G. (Box 920)
- Brahn (Box 921)
- Braithwaite (Box 922)
- Bramwell (Box 923)
- Brand, Olga, 1905- (Box 924)
- Brandes (Box 925)
- Brandstaetter, Christian (Box 926)
- Brandts (Box 927)
- Brant, Sebastian (Box 928)
- Brasil F.C. (Box 929)
- Brathwaite (Box 930)
- Brauer, O. (Box 931)
- Braun, S. (Box 932)
- Brave n. (Box 933)
- Brayda, B. (Box 934)
- Brazil. Congresso (Box 935)
- Brazil. Instituto (Box 936)
- Brazil. Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores (Box 937)
- Brasilia (Brazil). Universidade (Box 938)
- Breathless Diversions (Box 939)
- Brecht, C (Box 940)
- Bree, Germaine (Box 941)
- Breihan, Carl W., 1915- (Box 942)
- Bremer (Box 943)
- Brenes (Box 944)
- Brentano (Box 945)
- Brescia (Italy) (Box 946)
- Brest, France. Pontanezen Camp. (Box 947)
- Brett (Box 948)
- Breve (Box 949)
- Brewer, T. (Box 950)
- Brezhnev, Leonid Ilyich, 1906-1982 (continued) (Box 951)
- Bricklayer (Box 952)
- Bridges (surname) (Box 953)
- Brief (Box 954)
- Briefe (Box 955)
- Briffault, Eugene Victor, 1799-1854 (Box 956)
- Brigham (Box 957)
- Brigl (Box 958)
- Brine (Box 959)
- Brinkman's (Box 960)
- Bris, E. (Box 961)
- Bristol, Avon (Box 962)
- Britain in pictures (Box 963)
- British Academy (continued) (Box 964)
- British Association of (Box 965)
- British Columbia. Ministry of E. (Box 966)
- British economic crisis (Box 967)
- British Information Services (Box 968)
- British Library. Research (Box 969)
- British Museum. Department of Manuscripts. (Box 970)
- British museum (subject) (Box 971)
- British ornithologists (Box 972)
- British social (Box 973)
- Brite, R. (Box 974)
- Britton (law treatise) (Box 975)
- Broadmoor (Box 976)
- Broche (Box 977)
- Brocklesby (Box 978)
- Brodie (Box 979)
- Broedel (Box 980)
- Broke (Box 981)
- Bromme (Box 982)
- Bronson, J. (Box 983)
- Brook (Box 984)
- Brookes (Box 985)
- Brookings Institution. Studies in Administration (Box 986)
- Brooklyn Library (Box 987)
- Brooks, F. (Box 988)
- Brooks Van Wyck, 1886-1963 (Box 989)
- Brosse (Box 990)
- Brough (Box 991)
- Brousson (Box 992)
- Brown, Alison, 1934- (Box 993)
- Brown, Charles Rufus (Box 994)
- Brown, Francis Henry (Box 995)
- Brown, I. (Box 996)
- Brown, John, 1810-1882 (Box 997)
- Brown, Lew (Box 998)
- Brown, Philip Marshall (Box 999)
- Brown, Stanley (Box 1000)
- Brown, William Norman, 1892- (Box 1001)
- Browne, E. (Box 1002)
- Browne, S. (Box 1003)
- Browning, E. (Box 1004)
- Browning, Robert (subject) (G) (Box 1005)
- Broz, Ladislov (Box 1006)
- Bruce, W. (Box 1007)
- Brueckbauer, Frederick, 1864- (Box 1008)
- Bruen (Box 1009)
- Bruguier, Giuseppe (Box 1010)
- Brun, Georg, 1931- (Box 1011)
- Brunet (Box 1012)
- Brunn, Heinrich von (Box 1013)
- Bruno, E. (Box 1014)
- Brunswick (Duchy) (Box 1015)
- Brussels (author) (Box 1016)
- Brutus, Marcus Junius, B.C. 79 (ca)-42 (Box 1017)
- Bryan, J. (Box 1018)
- Bryant, W. (Box 1019)
- Bryhn, N. (Box 1020)
- Buachidze, G. (Box 1021)
- Buccleuch (Box 1022)
- Buchan, John, 1875-1940 (continued) (Box 1023)
- Buchar, J. (Box 1024)
- Buchholz Gallery, New York (Box 1025)
- Buck, Alonzo (Box 1026)
- Buckfast Abbey (Box 1027)
- Buckley (Box 1028)
- Bucyrus (Box 1029)
- Budd (Box 1030)
- Buddhist Oracle (Box 1031)
- Budich, Carl, 1904- (Box 1032)
- Buechner (Box 1033)
- Die Buehne (Box 1034)
- Bueno (Box 1035)
- Buenos Aires (titles, etc.) (Box 1036)
- Buesching (Box 1037)
- Buffalo General Electric Company (Box 1038)
- Bugnet (Box 1039)
- Building of a b. (Box 1040)
- Bukh (Box 1041)
- Bukkyo yogi (Box 1042)
- Bulfinch (Box 1043)
- Bulgarin, Fadel, 1789-1859 (Box 1044)
- Bulgarska voenna istoria (Box 1045)
- Bull, J. (Box 1046)
- Bulletin (Illinois State Water Survey) (continued) (Box 1047)
- Bulletin du (Box 1048)
- Bulletin Quotidien d'information Cambodia (Box 1049)
- Bullock, fund, limited. (Box 1050)
- Bulwer (Box 1051)
- Bundesarchiv (Germany (West)) (Box 1052)
- Bundy, Walter Ernest, 1889- (Box 1053)
- Bunina, F (Box 1054)
- Bunsen (Box 1055)
- Bunyan, John, 1628-1688 (Box 1056)
- Buraku Sabetsu Ishiki no Kenkyu (Box 1057)
- Burck (Box 1058)
- Burdick (Box 1059)
- Bureau Veritas (Box 1060)
- Burger (Box 1061)
- Burgess, J. (Box 1062)
- Burgos, Elisabeth (Box 1063)
- Buried Past (Box 1064)
- Burke, J. (Box 1065)
- Burkhardt (Box 1066)
- Burlingame (Box 1067)
- Burma, Lower (Box 1068)
- Burnand (Box 1069)
- Burnet, Gilbert (subject) (Box 1070)
- Burney, Fanny, 1752-1840 (Box 1071)
- Burns, Arthur Frank, 1904- (Box 1072)
- Burns, Robert-Appreciation (Box 1073)
- Burr, G. (Box 1074)
- Burroughs (Box 1075)
- Burrows (Box 1076)
- Burt, J. (Box 1077)
- Burton, M. (Box 1078)
- Bury (Box 1079)
- Busch, M. (Box 1080)
- Bush, M.L. (Box 1081)
- Bushong, Charles H. (Box 1082)
- Business Law and the Legal Environment (Box 1083)
- Buss, Edith H. (Box 1084)
- Bustamante, Carlos Maria de (subject) (Box 1085)
- Butchers (Box 1086)
- Butler, F. (Box 1087)
- Butler, Rachel Barton (Box 1088)
- Le Butor (Box 1089)
- Butterworth (Box 1090)
- Bux (Box 1091)
- By (Box 1092)
- Byfield (Box 1093)
- Byrd (Box 1094)
- Byron, George Gordon Noel, 1788-1824. Childe Harold's.. (Box 1095)
- Byron, George Gordon Noel, 1788-1824 (subject) (P) (Box 1096)
- Byzantine Empire (Author) (Box 1097)
- C., T. (Box 1098)
- C.E.L.A.D.E. (Box 1099)
- C.I.D.I.P. (Box 1100)
- C.O.S.P.A.R. (Box 1101)
- C.U.E.R.M.A. (Box 1102)
- Cabaraban, Magdalena C. (Box 1103)
- Cabinet Government in Australia (Box 1104)
- Cabral, Teodosio (Box 1105)
- Cactus (Box 1106)
- Cadiz (Box 1107)
- Caesar, C. (author) (Box 1108)
- Café en Costa Rica (Box 1109)
- Cahier (Box 1110)
- Cahiers de l'ONAREST (Box 1111)
- Cahiers G. (Box 1112)
- Caidin, M. (Box 1113)
- Caird, M. (Box 1114)
- Cairo, a practical guide (Box 1115)
- Calabria (Box 1116)
- Calculus (Box 1117)
- Caldera (Box 1118)
- Calderoni (Box 1119)
- Caledon (Box 1120)
- Calhoun, K. (Box 1121)
- California, D. (Box 1122)
- California. Railroad commission (Box 1123)
- California b. (Box 1124)
- California S. (Box 1125)
- Calkins, N. (Box 1126)
- Calle (Box 1127)
- Callis (Box 1128)
- Caloric engines (Box 1129)
- Calvin (Box 1130)
- Calvin, Jean, 1509-1564-Bibliography (Box 1131)
- Camacho O. (Box 1132)
- Cambio p. (Box 1133)
- Cambridge Bible (Box 1134)
- Cambridge studies (Box 1135)
- Camelot, P. (Box 1136)
- Cameron, Juan (Box 1137)
- Camilli, Ernesto (Box 1138)
- Camoin (Box 1139)
- Campaigns and Cruises (Box 1140)
- Campbell, Archibald (Box 1141)
- Campbell, J. (Box 1142)
- Campbell, R. (Box 1143)
- Campeche (Box 1144)
- Campo y Cielo (Box 1145)
- Camsell (Box 1146)
- Canada. Army Historical Selection (Box 1147)
- Canada. Canadian Army (Box 1148)
- Canada. Department of Mines (Box 1149)
- Canada. Laws, statutes, etc. (Box 1150)
- Canada. Public Archives (Box 1151)
- Canada Centre for Inland Waters (Box 1152)
- Canadian Association of Research Libraries (Box 1153)
- Canadian Forestry Service (Box 1154)
- Canadian Jubilee Singers (Box 1155)
- Canadian Railway (Box 1156)
- Canal-Zone (Box 1157)
- Cancer in the Young (Box 1158)
- Candidius (Box 1159)
- Canfield (Box 1160)
- Canning, George (Box 1161)
- Canova (Box 1162)
- Canterbury (titles, etc.) (Box 1163)
- Canton, O. (Box 1164)
- Cap (Box 1165)
- Cape of Good Hope. Parliament-Rules (Box 1166)
- Capelli, Gianni (Box 1167)
- Les Capitalismes (Box 1168)
- Capograssi, Giuseppe, 1889-1956 (Box 1169)
- Caprara (Box 1170)
- Capuchins (Box 1171)
- Caradec, Francois (Box 1172)
- Carberry (Box 1173)
- Carcopino (Box 1174)
- Cardinal, Agnes (Box 1175)
- Carducci, Giosue (Box 1176)
- Carey, F. (Box 1177)
- Caribbean (Box 1178)
- Carl (Box 1179)
- Carletti, Giuseppe (Box 1180)
- Carlos (Box 1181)
- Carlton (Box 1182)
- Carman, Bliss (Box 1183)
- Carmina Lyrica (Box 1184)
- Carnegie Commission on Higher Education (continued) (Box 1185)
- Carnegie Endowment. Library (Box 1186)
- Carnegie Institution. Report (Box 1187)
- Carney (Box 1188)
- Carolina (Box 1189)
- Carp (Box 1190)
- Carpenter, S. (Box 1191)
- Carr, E. (Box 1192)
- Carranza (Box 1193)
- Carrera (Box 1194)
- Carrigan (Box 1195)
- Carroll, D. (Box 1196)
- Carrossel (Box 1197)
- Carrs (Box 1198)
- Cartas de Liberdade (Box 1199)
- Carter, George (Box 1200)
- Carter, Ronald (Box 1201)
- Cartmel Priory (Box 1202)
- Carus, P. (Box 1203)
- Carver (Box 1204)
- Carysfort (Box 1205)
- Casalegno (Box 1206)
- Casasanta (Box 1207)
- Case c. (Box 1208)
- Case t. (Box 1209)
- Cashel (Box 1210)
- Caspar (Box 1211)
- Cassel (Box 1212)
- Cassidore (Box 1213)
- Castagnez (Box 1214)
- Castell (Box 1215)
- Castello Branco (continued) (Box 1216)
- Castiglioni, C. (Box 1217)
- Castillo Salaverry, E. (Box 1218)
- Castorina, D. (Box 1219)
- Castro, H. (Box 1220)
- Castruccio (Box 1221)
- Catalogue of books on angling (Box 1222)
- Catalogue of the E. (Box 1223)
- Catalogo de t. (Box 1224)
- Catalonia (Box 1225)
- Catedral de Leon (Box 1226)
- Cather, W., O Pioneers (Box 1227)
- Catholic church. Breviary (Box 1228)
- Catholic church. Catechism (continued) (Box 1229)
- Catholic church. Legates (continued) (Box 1230)
- Catholic church. Liturgy and Ritual, Bibliography (Box 1231)
- Catholic church. Pope, 1700-1721 (Clemens XI) (Box 1232)
- Catholic church-Bibliography (Box 1233)
- Catholic church-Catholic authors (Box 1234)
- Catholic church-Doctrinal… 19th cent. (Box 1235)
- Catholic church-History 1789-1900 (Box 1236)
- Catholic church-Relations (dip.) (Box 1237)
- Catholic church-Relations (dip.) (continued) (Box 1238)
- Catholic M. (Box 1239)
- Catholic University of America. School of Canon Law (Box 1240)
- Cato major (Box 1241)
- Cattelle (Box 1242)
- Caucasian (Box 1243)
- Cause of the S. (Box 1244)
- Cavalcanti, G.H. (Box 1245)
- Cavazza, F. (Box 1246)
- Caviglia, B. (Box 1247)
- Cayatte, A. (Box 1248)
- Cazza (Box 1249)
- Cech (Box 1250)
- Cejador (Box 1251)
- Celia Montalvan (Box 1252)
- Cellini, Benvenuto (author) (Box 1253)
- Cence, R.J., 1930- (Box 1254)
- Census occupations (Box 1255)
- Centennial hist. (Box 1256)
- Center for M. (Box 1257)
- Center paper (continued) (Box 1258)
- Central association (Box 1259)
- Central Miss. (Box 1260)
- Centralstelle (Box 1261)
- Centre d'etudes L. (Box 1262)
- Centre de science (Box 1263)
- Centre nat. de la recherce G. (Box 1264)
- Centro (Box 1265)
- Centro de Estudos (Box 1266)
- Centro di studi di ragioneria (Box 1267)
- Centro Palatino (Box 1268)
- Century of Hardware and Steel (Box 1269)
- Cercle de la Librairie (France) (Box 1270)
- Cerise (Box 1271)
- Certain (Box 1272)
- Cervantes, Miguel de. Don Quixote. Translations. English Translation (continued) (Box 1273)
- Cervantes (subject) Technique (Box 1274)
- Ceska Akademie ved a Umeni, Prague (Box 1275)
- Ceskoslovenska Akademie Zemedelska, Prague (Box 1276)
- Cesty Moderni Jazykovedy (Box 1277)
- Cezanne (Box 1278)
- Chabot, Denys, 1945- (Box 1279)
- Chadwick, G. (Box 1280)
- Chagall et le Theatre (Box 1281)
- Chaine (Box 1282)
- Chalcocandylas, Laonicus (Box 1283)
- Challenger (Box 1284)
- Chalochet, Pierre-Henri (Box 1285)
- Chamberlain (Box 1286)
- Chamberlayne, Charles Frederic, 1855- (Box 1287)
- Chambers, R. (Box 1288)
- Chambrun (Box 1289)
- Champdor (Box 1290)
- Champollion-Figeac (Box 1291)
- Chan Shih Hsin Li Hsueh (Box 1292)
- Chand, Amar (Box 1293)
- Chandra (Box 1294)
- Chang, Chen-to (Box 1295)
- Chang, Chien, 1939- (continued) (Box 1296)
- Chang, Chun (Box 1297)
- Chang, Hen-shui, 1895- (continued) (Box 1298)
- Chang, Hu (Box 1299)
- Chang, Ku-fu (Box 1300)
- Chang, Mi (Box 1301)
- Chang, Shao-nan (Box 1302)
- Chang, T'ang (Box 1303)
- Chang, Tzu-k'ai, 1900- (Box 1304)
- Chang, Yu-te (Box 1305)
- Changing Campaign Techniques (Box 1306)
- Channing (Box 1307)
- Chant (Titles, Phrases, etc.) (Box 1308)
- Chao, Chih-yang (Box 1309)
- Chao, K. (Box 1310)
- Chao, T. (Box 1311)
- Chapais (Box 1312)
- Chaplin, C. (Box 1313)
- Chapman, George, 1723-1806 (Box 1314)
- Chapman, W. (Box 1315)
- Chapus (Box 1316)
- Charbonneux, Jean, 1895-1969 (Box 1317)
- Charities (Titles, etc.) (Box 1318)
- Charles I, 1600-1649 (subject) (G) (Box 1319)
- Charles IV (Box 1320)
- Charles, T. (Box 1321)
- Charleston, S.C. Department (Box 1322)
- Charlotte de Silenie (Box 1323)
- Charpentier (Box 1324)
- Charters, W. (Box 1325)
- Chase, G. (Box 1326)
- Chasles (Box 1327)
- Chateau d'Eu (Box 1328)
- Chatelard, Yvette (Box 1329)
- Chatterton, T. (Box 1330)
- Chaucer, Geoffrey. Canterbury Tales. Selections. Pollard ed. (Box 1331)
- Chaucer, G. (subject) (Box 1332)
- Chaumont (Box 1333)
- Chautemos (Box 1334)
- Chavez, F. (Box 1335)
- Ch'e chin K'ao (Box 1336)
- Checkley (Box 1337)
- Cheffaud (Box 1338)
- Chekov, A. (continued) (Box 1339)
- Chemical abstracts (Box 1340)
- Chemical Society (continued) (Box 1341)
- Chemistry of m.n.p. (Box 1342)
- Chen Chi (Box 1343)
- Ch'en, Chin-po (Box 1344)
- Chen, H. (Box 1345)
- Ch'en hun chi (Box 1346)
- Ch'en, K'uei-lin (Box 1347)
- Ch'en-na (Box 1348)
- Ch'en, Sheng-I (Box 1349)
- Chen Ti (Box 1350)
- Chen, Wen-haing (Box 1351)
- Chenain (Box 1352)
- Cheng, Ch'eng-haun (Box 1353)
- Ch'eng, Ch'ing-t'ai (Box 1354)
- Cheng, Hsuan (Box 1355)
- Ch'eng, Nai-ch'ien (Box 1356)
- Cheng, Tong Y. (Box 1357)
- Chennault, A. (Box 1358)
- Cherfils (Box 1359)
- Chernov, Yu. I. (Box 1360)
- Cherry, T.A.F. (Box 1361)
- Chesneau (Box 1362)
- Chesterfield, P. (Box 1363)
- Chesterton, G. (Box 1364)
- Chevalier, M. (Box 1365)
- Chey, Youn-cha (Box 1366)
- Ch'i chieh (Box 1367)
- Chi jen yen fu (Box 1368)
- Chi nien ti (Box 1369)
- Chi wai (Box 1370)
- Chia, L. (Box 1371)
- Chiang, Ch'ing (Box 1372)
- Chiang hu nu (Box 1373)
- Chiang, Lan (Box 1374)
- Chiang su nan… (Box 1375)
- Chiang, Yang,1681-1762 (Box 1376)
- Ch'iao wu pao (Box 1377)
- Chiavenna, A. (Box 1378)
- Chicago (continued) (Box 1379)
- Chicago centennial (Box 1380)
- Chicago, St. Charles and Mississippi Air-Line Railroad (Box 1381)
- Chida, Chojiro (Box 1382)
- Chien (Box 1383)
- Chien hsing chi (Box 1384)
- Chien Mu-yin (Box 1385)
- Chien Yi-tzuu (Box 1386)
- Ch'ih, Fang (Box 1387)
- Chiho jichi (Box 1388)
- Chikusai (Box 1389)
- Child development (Box 1390)
- Children in collectives (Box 1391)
- Childs (Titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 1392)
- Chile, Laws, etc. (Box 1393)
- Chile: el desafio (Box 1394)
- Chin (author) (Box 1395)
- Chin, Ming (Box 1396)
- Chin-ching (Box 1397)
- Ch'in lu (Box 1398)
- Chin tai Chung-Kuo (continued) (Box 1399)
- Ch'in ting (Box 1400)
- China. Laws, statutes, etc. (continued) (Box 1401)
- China, Chung-Kuo (Box 1402)
- China, Inspectorate (Box 1403)
- China, Nung K'en pu (Box 1404)
- China (Rep. of China) (Box 1405)
- China (titles, etc.) (Box 1406)
- China news (Box 1407)
- China's voice (Box 1408)
- Chinese folk arts (Box 1409)
- Chinese University of Hong K. (Box 1410)
- Ching chi (Box 1411)
- Ch'ing fu (Box 1412)
- Ching -lai Shen (Box 1413)
- Ching shih pao (Box 1414)
- Ching Wen (Box 1415)
- Chipman (Box 1416)
- Chisholm, J. (Box 1417)
- Chitty, J. (Box 1418)
- Ch'iu, L. (Box 1419)
- Chizawa, T. (Box 1420)
- Choate, R. (Box 1421)
- Choice, chance and change (Box 1422)
- Cholnoky (Box 1423)
- Chopin, Fryderyk Francisyek (Box 1424)
- Chosen Highway (Box 1425)
- Chou (Box 1426)
- Chou, Erh-fu (Box 1427)
- Chou, Kʻai-chʻing (Box 1428)
- Chou, Pu-mi (Box 1429)
- Chou, Yu-chin (Box 1430)
- Chree (Box 1431)
- Christ in a Poncho (Box 1432)
- Christian V, King of Denmark, 1646-1699 (Box 1433)
- Christian Keepsake (Box 1434)
- Christianity and Race (Box 1435)
- Christie, Octavius Francis, 1867- (Box 1436)
- Christmas (Titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 1437)
- Christophers (Box 1438)
- Chronicle of the Isles (Box 1439)
- Chroniques Martiniennes (Box 1440)
- Chu, Chen-hsin (Box 1441)
- Chu, Chung-chieh (Box 1442)
- Chu, Hsu (Box 1443)
- Chu, Lien, 1828-1904 (Box 1444)
- Chu-So tairitsu nempyo (Box 1445)
- Chu Tzu-ching, 1898-1948 (Box 1446)
- Chu, Yuan (continued) (Box 1447)
- Ch'uan Kuo Hai Pao Ta Chan Chuan Chi (Box 1448)
- Chuang (Box 1449)
- Chuang Wai (Box 1450)
- Chugoku (Box 1451)
- Chugoku No Keizai (Box 1452)
- Chuiko, Havrylo A. (Box 1453)
- Chun (Box 1454)
- Chun-jen (continued) (Box 1455)
- Chung-chih (Box 1456)
- Chung Hu (Box 1457)
- Chung-hua Min Kuo Chiao Yu Hua K'an (Box 1458)
- Chung-hua Shu Chu (continued) (Box 1459)
- Chung Jih Kuan Hsi Shih ti Hsin P'ien Chang (continued) (Box 1460)
- Chung Kung Ti Hsueh Hsiao Chiao Yu (Box 1461)
- Chung-Kuo Chih Hui Tui (Box 1462)
- Chung-Kuo Ch'ing Nien Ch'u Pan She (continued) (Box 1463)
- Chung-Kuo Fang Chih Ts'ung Shu Hua-chung Ti Fang (continued) (Box 1464)
- Chung-Kuo Hsien Tai Hua Ti Lu (continued) (Box 1465)
- Chung-Kuo hua yuan (Box 1466)
- Chung-Kuo Kao liang (Box 1467)
- Chung-Kuo K'o hsueh (Box 1468)
- Chung-Kuo Ku tien wen (continued) (Box 1469)
- Chung-Kuo Kung ch'an tang (Box 1470)
- Chung-Kuo Kung ch'an ti mi mi (Box 1471)
- Chung-Kuo Kuo shu chih (Box 1472)
- Chung-Kuo min chien yu yen (Box 1473)
- Chung-Kuo sang ti shih (Box 1474)
- Chung-Kuo shih pao (Box 1475)
- Chung-Kuo ti fang shih chih hsieh hui (Box 1476)
- Chung-Kuo t'u ti wen t'i (Box 1477)
- Chung-Kuo wen i hsieh hui (Box 1478)
- Chung, Mei-yin (Box 1479)
- Chung, T'ung-shan (Box 1480)
- Chung, yang tang an kuan (Box 1481)
- Chung yang yin hang (Box 1482)
- Chuquet (Box 1483)
- Church and state (titles) (Box 1484)
- Church of England. Book of common prayer (1800) (Box 1485)
- Church of England (Diocese…) (Box 1486)
- Church of England (Convocations and synods) (Box 1487)
- Church of England (titles) (Box 1488)
- Church of Scotland (continued) (Box 1489)
- Churchill, E. (Box 1490)
- Churchman (Box 1491)
- Chushoran (Box 1492)
- Ciampi (Box 1493)
- Cibber, Colley (subject) (Box 1494)
- Cicero, Marcus Tullius (De Officiis) (Box 1495)
- Cicero, Pro Balbo (Box 1496)
- Cid (Box 1497)
- Ciervo (Box 1498)
- Cincinnati, O. (author) (Box 1499)
- Cine Venezolano (Box 1500)
- Cintra, Assis (Box 1501)
- Circular (Box 1502)
- Cisneros, Carlos B. (Box 1503)
- Citizen of New England (Box 1504)
- Citta (Box 1505)
- City of Benin (Box 1506)
- Ciusa, N. (Box 1507)
- Civil wars in… (Box 1508)
- Clacius (Box 1509)
- Clairvoyant Goat (Box 1510)
- Clapton (Box 1511)
- Claridge (Box 1512)
- Clark, Chester (Box 1513)
- Clark, Glenn (Box 1514)
- Clark, John W. (Box 1515)
- Clark, Robert J. (Box 1516)
- Clark, William Andrews (Box 1517)
- Clarke, Donald (Box 1518)
- Clarke, John (Box 1519)
- Clarke, William (Box 1520)
- Clasper, James W. (Box 1521)
- Classical journal (Box 1522)
- Classisch (Box 1523)
- Claudin (Box 1524)
- Clauswitz (Box 1525)
- Clay, Henry, 1777-1852 (Box 1526)
- Claytor (Box 1527)
- Cleghorn (Box 1528)
- Clemens, Titus Flavius, Alexandrinus (Box 1529)
- Clements (Box 1530)
- Clerget (Box 1531)
- Cleveland, L. (Box 1532)
- Clewes (Box 1533)
- Clim, Yoshimi (Box 1534)
- Clinical neuro-urology (Box 1535)
- Clocchiatti, Amerigo (Box 1536)
- Clot (Artist) (Box 1537)
- Clow (Box 1538)
- Clunet (Box 1539)
- Coady (Box 1540)
- Coastal range (Box 1541)
- Cobb, L. (Box 1542)
- Cobbett, William, 1763-1835 (continued) (Box 1543)
- Coburn, James M. (Box 1544)
- Cochran, L.E. (Box 1545)
- Cockerell, T. (Box 1546)
- Coddington (Box 1547)
- Codex venetus grecus VII (Box 1548)
- Coe, Ralph T. (Box 1549)
- Coeur (Box 1550)
- Coffman, P. (Box 1551)
- Cogswell (Box 1552)
- Cohen, G. (Box 1553)
- Cohen, M. (Box 1554)
- Cohen, Y. (Box 1555)
- Cohon (Box 1556)
- Coke, Thomas (Box 1557)
- Colby (surname) (Box 1558)
- Cole, B. (Box 1559)
- Cole, L. (Box 1560)
- Colecao CEDEC (Box 1561)
- Colecao Realidade edu. (Box 1562)
- Coleccion CEIS (Box 1563)
- Coleccion de memorias… (Box 1564)
- Coleccion H. (Box 1565)
- Coleccion N. (Box 1566)
- Coleccion U. (Box 1567)
- Coleman, J. (Box 1568)
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor (author) (Box 1569)
- Coles, L. (Box 1570)
- Colijn, P. (Box 1571)
- Collana di saggi (Box 1572)
- Colleccion Musica (Box 1573)
- Collection (Box 1574)
- Collection de memories (Box 1575)
- Collection H. (Box 1576)
- Collection of early (Box 1577)
- Collection R. (Box 1578)
- Collections E. (Box 1579)
- College entomology (Box 1580)
- Collegium (Box 1581)
- Collezione T. (Box 1582)